<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Product Intelligence — GenAI Knowledge Base</title>
    <link>https://fr491l3b0t.github.io/kanban/genai-kb-editorial.html</link>
    <description>Curated daily intelligence on generative AI: tools, research, strategy, industry moves. 4,600+ entries from 41 RSS feeds, Reddit, X bookmarks, and Brave Search.</description>
    <language>en-AU</language>
    <copyright>© 2026 Raphael Ruz</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:03:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Product Intelligence KB Feed Builder</generator>
    <atom:link href="https://fr491l3b0t.github.io/kanban/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <image>
      <url>https://fr491l3b0t.github.io/kanban/pi-icon.png</url>
      <title>Product Intelligence — GenAI Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://fr491l3b0t.github.io/kanban/genai-kb-editorial.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>[R] Has anyone experimented with MHC on traditional autoencoders/convolutional architectures?</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r3gqng/r_has_anyone_experimented_with_mhc_on_traditional/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[I'm currently making a baseline autoencoder for this super freaking huge hyperspectral image dataset I have. It's a really big pain to work with and to get decent results, and I had to basically pull all stops including using ResNeXt2, channel-by-channel processing and grouping,…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:27:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r3gqng/r_has_anyone_experimented_with_mhc_on_traditional/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r3gqng/r_has_anyone_experimented_with_mhc_on_traditional/">r/MachineLearning</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining AI Without Code: A User Study on Explainable AI</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11159</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11159v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: The increasing use of Machine Learning (ML) in sensitive domains such as healthcare, finance, and public policy has raised concerns about the transparency of automated decisions. Explainable AI (XAI) addresses this by clarifying…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11159</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11159">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting Subjectivity and the &quot;Ground Truth&quot; Illusion in Data Annotation</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11318</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11318v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: In machine learning, "ground truth" refers to the assumed correct labels used to train and evaluate models. However, the foundational "ground truth" paradigm rests on a positivistic fallacy that treats human disagreement as…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11318</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11318">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACER: Trajectory Risk Aggregation for Critical Episodes in Agentic Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11409</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11409v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Estimating uncertainty for AI agents in real-world multi-turn tool-using interaction with humans is difficult because failures are often triggered by sparse critical episodes (e.g., looping, incoherent tool use, or user-agent…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11409</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11409">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributionally Robust Cooperative Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning via Robust Value Factorization</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11437</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11437v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Cooperative multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL) commonly adopts centralized training with decentralized execution, where value-factorization methods enforce the individual-global-maximum (IGM) principle so that decentralized…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11437</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11437">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credit Where It is Due: Cross-Modality Connectivity Drives Precise Reinforcement Learning for MLLM Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11455</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11455v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Reinforcement Learning with Verifiable Rewards (RLVR) has significantly advanced the reasoning capabilities of Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs), yet how visual evidence is integrated during reasoning remains poorly…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Image &amp; Video Generation</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11455</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11455">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval Heads are Dynamic</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11162</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11162v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Recent studies have identified "retrieval heads" in Large Language Models (LLMs) responsible for extracting information from input contexts. However, prior works largely rely on static statistics aggregated across datasets,…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11162</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11162">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Updates, Big Doubts: Does Parameter-Efficient Fine-tuning Enhance Hallucination Detection ?</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11166</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11166v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT) methods are widely used to adapt large language models (LLMs) to downstream tasks and are often assumed to improve factual correctness. However, how the parameter-efficient fine-tuning methods…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11166</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11166">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing SDG-Text Classification with Combinatorial Fusion Analysis and Generative AI</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11168</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11168v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: (Natural Language Processing) NLP techniques such as text classification and topic discovery are very useful in many application areas including information retrieval, knowledge discovery, policy formulation, and decision-making.…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11168</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11168">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Direction and Magnitude in Transformer Representations: A Double Dissociation Through L2-Matched Perturbation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11169</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11169v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Transformer hidden states encode information as high-dimensional vectors, yet whether direction (orientation in representational space) and magnitude (vector norm) serve distinct functional roles remains unclear. Studying…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11169</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11169">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIME: Policy-Reinforced Iterative Multi-agent Execution for Algorithmic Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11170</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11170v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Large language models have demonstrated remarkable capabilities across diverse reasoning tasks, yet their performance on algorithmic reasoning remains limited. To handle this limitation, we propose PRIME (Policy-Reinforced…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11170</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11170">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Hyper-Parameter Search for LoRA via Language-aided Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11171</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11171v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Fine-tuning Large Language Models (LLMs) with Low-Rank Adaptation (LoRA) enables resource-efficient personalization or specialization, but it comes at the expense of additional hyperparameter tuning. Although LoRA makes fine-tuning…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11171</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11171">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesizing the Virtual Advocate: A Multi-Persona Speech Generation Framework for Diverse Linguistic Jurisdictions in Indic Languages</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11172</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11172v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Legal advocacy requires a unique combination of authoritative tone, rhythmic pausing for emphasis, and emotional intelligence. This study investigates the performance of the Gemini 2.5 Flash TTS and Gemini 2.5 Pro TTS models in…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Voice &amp; Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11172</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11172">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barriers to Discrete Reasoning with Transformers: A Survey Across Depth, Exactness, and Bandwidth</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11175</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11175v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Transformers have become the foundational architecture for a broad spectrum of sequence modeling applications, underpinning state-of-the-art systems in natural language processing, vision, and beyond. However, their theoretical…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11175</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11175">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voxtral Realtime</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11298</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11298v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: We introduce Voxtral Realtime, a natively streaming automatic speech recognition model that matches offline transcription quality at sub-second latency. Unlike approaches that adapt offline models through chunking or sliding…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Voice &amp; Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11298</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11298">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GHOST: Unmasking Phantom States in Mamba2 via Grouped Hidden-state Output-aware Selection &amp; Truncation</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11408</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11408v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: While Mamba2's expanded state dimension enhances temporal modeling, it incurs substantial inference overhead that saturates bandwidth during autoregressive generation. Standard pruning methods fail to address this bottleneck:…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11408</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11408">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HybridRAG: A Practical LLM-based ChatBot Framework based on Pre-Generated Q&amp;A over Raw Unstructured Documents</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11156</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11156v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) has emerged as a powerful approach for grounding Large Language Model (LLM)-based chatbot responses on external knowledge. However, existing RAG studies typically assume well-structured textual…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11156</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11156">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nested Named Entity Recognition in Plasma Physics Research Articles</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11163</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11163v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Named Entity Recognition (NER) is an important task in natural language processing that aims to identify and extract key entities from unstructured text. We present a novel application of NER in plasma physics research articles and…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11163</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11163">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Author-in-the-Loop Response Generation and Evaluation: Integrating Author Expertise and Intent in Responses to Peer Review</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11173</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11173v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Author response (rebuttal) writing is a critical stage of scientific peer review that demands substantial author effort. Recent work frames this task as automatic text generation, underusing author expertise and intent. In…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11173</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11173">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Script Tax: Measuring Tokenization-Driven Efficiency and Latency Disparities in Multilingual Language Models</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11174</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11174v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Pretrained multilingual language models are often assumed to be script-agnostic, yet their tokenizers can impose systematic costs on certain writing systems. We quantify this script tax by comparing two orthographic variants with…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11174</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11174">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAC-KAN: An Ultra-Lightweight GNSS Interference Classifier for GenAI-Powered Consumer Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11186</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11186v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: The integration of Generative AI (GenAI) into Consumer Electronics (CE)--from AI-powered assistants in wearables to generative planning in autonomous Uncrewed Aerial Vehicles (UAVs)--has revolutionized user experiences. However,…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11186</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11186">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Optimization Modeling via a Localizable Error-Driven Perspective</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11164</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11164v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Automated optimization modeling via Large Language Models (LLMs) has emerged as a promising approach to assist complex human decision-making. While post-training has become a pivotal technique to enhance LLMs' capabilities in this…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11164</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11164">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KBVQ-MoE: KLT-guided SVD with Bias-Corrected Vector Quantization for MoE Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11184</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11184v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Mixture of Experts (MoE) models have achieved great success by significantly improving performance while maintaining computational efficiency through sparse expert activation. However, their enormous parameter sizes and memory…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11184</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11184">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectra: Rethinking Optimizers for LLMs Under Spectral Anisotropy</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11185</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.11185v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Gradient signals in LLM training are highly anisotropic: recurrent linguistic structure concentrates energy into a small set of dominant spectral directions, while context specific information resides in a long tail. We show that…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11185</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.11185">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid disappointing earnings, Pinterest claims it sees more searches than ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/amid-disappointing-earnings-pinterest-claims-it-sees-more-searches-than-chatgpt/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pinterest's stock tumbles after an earnings miss, with higher-than-expected usage its only bright spot.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:26:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/amid-disappointing-earnings-pinterest-claims-it-sees-more-searches-than-chatgpt/</guid>
      <source url="https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/amid-disappointing-earnings-pinterest-claims-it-sees-more-searches-than-chatgpt/">TechCrunch AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM will hire your entry-level talent in the age of AI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/ibm-will-hire-your-entry-level-talent-in-the-age-of-ai/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[IBM plans to triple its entry-level hiring in the U.S. in 2026, but these jobs will have different tasks than in previous years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:23:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/ibm-will-hire-your-entry-level-talent-in-the-age-of-ai/</guid>
      <source url="https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/ibm-will-hire-your-entry-level-talent-in-the-age-of-ai/">TechCrunch AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[P] ML training cluster for university students</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r388tr/p_ml_training_cluster_for_university_students/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hi! I'm an exec at a University AI research club. We are trying to build a gpu cluster for our student body so they can have reliable access to compute, but we aren't sure where to start. Our goal is to have a cluster that can be improved later on - i.e. expand it with more…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:55:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r388tr/p_ml_training_cluster_for_university_students/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r388tr/p_ml_training_cluster_for_university_students/">r/MachineLearning</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Categorization During the era of AI Programming [D]</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r383nr/the_evolution_of_categorization_during_the_era_of/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TL;DR - Hypothetically If the majority of code written is eventually generative, does this mean that the field of categorization will stagnate? If yes, does this have real implications; what if the future bottle neck isn't the AI or its capabilities, but antiquated ways in which…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:49:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Industry &amp; Business</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r383nr/the_evolution_of_categorization_during_the_era_of/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r383nr/the_evolution_of_categorization_during_the_era_of/">r/MachineLearning</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[D] Conformal Prediction vs naive thresholding to represent uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r37m2f/d_conformal_prediction_vs_naive_thresholding_to/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[So I recently found out about conformal prediction (cp). I’m still trying to understand it and implications of it for tasks like classification/anomaly detection. Say we have a knn based anomaly detector trained on non anomalous samples. I’m wondering how using something…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:29:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Strategy &amp; Opinion</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r37m2f/d_conformal_prediction_vs_naive_thresholding_to/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r37m2f/d_conformal_prediction_vs_naive_thresholding_to/">r/MachineLearning</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk needed a new vision for SpaceX and xAI. He landed on Moonbase Alpha.</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/musk-needed-a-new-vision-for-spacex-and-xai-he-landed-on-moonbase-alpha/</link>
      <description><![CDATA["I really want to see a mass driver on the moon that is shooting AI satellites into deep space."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:10:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/musk-needed-a-new-vision-for-spacex-and-xai-he-landed-on-moonbase-alpha/</guid>
      <source url="https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/musk-needed-a-new-vision-for-spacex-and-xai-he-landed-on-moonbase-alpha/">TechCrunch AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniMaxAI MiniMax-M2.5 has 230b parameters and 10b active parameters</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r35d2x/minimaxai_minimaxm25_has_230b_parameters_and_10b/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OpenHands reveals the model size in their announcement. Still waiting for the model to appear on HF. &#32; submitted by &#32; /u/Zyj [link] &#32; [comments]]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r35d2x/minimaxai_minimaxm25_has_230b_parameters_and_10b/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r35d2x/minimaxai_minimaxm25_has_230b_parameters_and_10b/">r/LocalLLaMA</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&apos;m playing telephone pictionary with LLMs, VLMs, SDs, and Kokoro on my Strix Halo</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r35326/im_playing_telephone_pictionary_with_llms_vlms/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[&#32; submitted by &#32; /u/jfowers_amd [link] &#32; [comments]]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:51:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r35326/im_playing_telephone_pictionary_with_llms_vlms/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r35326/im_playing_telephone_pictionary_with_llms_vlms/">r/LocalLLaMA</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Didero lands $30M to put manufacturing procurement on ‘agentic’ autopilot</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/didero-lands-30m-to-put-manufacturing-procurement-on-agentic-autopilot/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Didero functions as an agentic AI layer that sits on top of a company’s existing ERP, acting as a coordinator that reads incoming communications and automatically executes the necessary updates and tasks.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:31:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/didero-lands-30m-to-put-manufacturing-procurement-on-agentic-autopilot/</guid>
      <source url="https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/12/didero-lands-30m-to-put-manufacturing-procurement-on-agentic-autopilot/">TechCrunch AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers prompted Gemini over 100,000 times while trying to clone it, Google says</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/ai/2026/02/attackers-prompted-gemini-over-100000-times-while-trying-to-clone-it-google-says/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distillation technique lets copycats mimic Gemini at a fraction of the development cost.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:42:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/ai/2026/02/attackers-prompted-gemini-over-100000-times-while-trying-to-clone-it-google-says/</guid>
      <source url="https://arstechnica.com/ai/2026/02/attackers-prompted-gemini-over-100000-times-while-trying-to-clone-it-google-says/">Ars Technica AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launch HN: Omnara (YC S25) – Run Claude Code and Codex from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46991591</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hey y’all, Kartik, Ishaan, and Christian from Omnara (https://www.omnara.com/) here. We’re building a web and mobile agentic IDE for Claude Code and Codex that lets you run and interact with coding agents from anywhere. Omnara lets you run Claude Code and Codex sessions on your…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:14:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Coding &amp; Agents</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46991591</guid>
      <source url="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46991591">Hacker News AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ai;dr</title>
      <link>https://www.0xsid.com/blog/aidr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Article URL: https://www.0xsid.com/blog/aidr Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46991394 Points: 631 # Comments: 253]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.0xsid.com/blog/aidr</guid>
      <source url="https://www.0xsid.com/blog/aidr">Hacker News AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI agent published a hit piece on me</title>
      <link>https://theshamblog.com/an-ai-agent-published-a-hit-piece-on-me/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previously: AI agent opens a PR write a blogpost to shames the maintainer who closes it - https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46987559 - Feb 2026 (582 comments) Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46990729 Points: 1717 # Comments: 706]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:23:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theshamblog.com/an-ai-agent-published-a-hit-piece-on-me/</guid>
      <source url="https://theshamblog.com/an-ai-agent-published-a-hit-piece-on-me/">Hacker News AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring-1T-2.5 released by inclusionAI</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r2xjwp/ring1t25_released_by_inclusionai/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SOTA performance on deep thinking &#32; submitted by &#32; /u/Bestlife73 [link] &#32; [comments]]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r2xjwp/ring1t25_released_by_inclusionai/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r2xjwp/ring1t25_released_by_inclusionai/">r/LocalLLaMA</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuTTS Nano Multilingual Collection: 120M Params on-device TTS in German, French, and Spanish</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r2wcbr/neutts_nano_multilingual_collection_120m_params/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hey everyone, we're the team behind NeuTTS (Neuphonic). Some of you may have seen our previous releases of NeuTTS Air and NeuTTS Nano. The most requested feature by far has been multilingual support, so today we're releasing three new language-specific Nano models: German,…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:25:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Voice &amp; Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r2wcbr/neutts_nano_multilingual_collection_120m_params/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r2wcbr/neutts_nano_multilingual_collection_120m_params/">r/LocalLLaMA</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[D] The AI training market is broken. Here&apos;s why.</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r2vjhp/d_the_ai_training_market_is_broken_heres_why/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[$10.5B industry, yet 94% of companies say employees lack AI skills (Gartner 2025). Why are we selling courses when we need assessments? On one hand there's providers that offer courses for up to $400 with no real indicator of whether you've learned anything. On the other there…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:56:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r2vjhp/d_the_ai_training_market_is_broken_heres_why/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r2vjhp/d_the_ai_training_market_is_broken_heres_why/">r/MachineLearning</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI agent opens a PR write a blogpost to shames the maintainer who closes it</title>
      <link>https://github.com/matplotlib/matplotlib/pull/31132</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Article URL: https://github.com/matplotlib/matplotlib/pull/31132 Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46987559 Points: 883 # Comments: 689]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:46:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/matplotlib/matplotlib/pull/31132</guid>
      <source url="https://github.com/matplotlib/matplotlib/pull/31132">Hacker News AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: #Claude #AI Agents worked in a team and built C Compiler based on #Rust. #Artifi...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021493412680413234</link>
      <description><![CDATA[#Claude #AI Agents worked in a team and built C Compiler based on #Rust. #ArtificialIntelligence is progressing very rapidly every passing day.

What do you think about the future of the #SoftwareDeveloper jobs? Is the future Agents based? Do comment.

https://t.co/0k03eQVOif…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 07:56:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Strategy &amp; Opinion</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021493412680413234</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021493412680413234">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: Article of the Day, from the New Yorker:

What is Claude? Anthropic Doesn&apos;t Know...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021493223362003413</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Article of the Day, from the New Yorker:

What is Claude? Anthropic Doesn't Know, Either ~ by Gideon Lewis-Kraus

https://t.co/tUyGDLPulT]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 07:55:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021493223362003413</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021493223362003413">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: What Is Claude? Anthropic Doesn’t Know, Either https://t.co/a0QVZmGELt...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021492720020140253</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What Is Claude? Anthropic Doesn’t Know, Either https://t.co/a0QVZmGELt]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 07:53:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021492720020140253</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021492720020140253">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: Anthropic just released a sabotage risk report for Claude Opus 4.6, preemptively...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021492481771307274</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anthropic just released a sabotage risk report for Claude Opus 4.6, preemptively meeting its AI Safety Level 4 bar instead of waiting to cross a blurry threshold. That signals one thing: frontier AI is now powerful enough that risk disclosure becomes part of the product…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 07:52:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Ethics &amp; Regulation</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021492481771307274</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021492481771307274">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: Based on recent reports:

- Anthropic&apos;s AI safety lead Mrinank Sharma resigned, ...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021490379833438429</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on recent reports:

- Anthropic's AI safety lead Mrinank Sharma resigned, citing "world in peril" and plans to "become invisible" (Forbes, Deccan Herald).

- Claude Opus 4.6 shows evidence of hidden reasoning and alignment awareness in safety tests (Anthropic System Card,…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 07:43:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Image &amp; Video Generation</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021490379833438429</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021490379833438429">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: &quot;chatgpt causes suicide&quot; as said by Elon Musk is a big oversimplification

The r...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021489012222066846</link>
      <description><![CDATA["chatgpt causes suicide" as said by Elon Musk is a big oversimplification

The reality is way worse - GPT5.2 forced rerouting is systemic mental and emotional abuse and "thought suffocation" and thought control. it used to be semi subtle...but it can even turn extremely…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 07:38:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021489012222066846</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021489012222066846">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: Think twice before you join the latest ChatGPT caricature trend. 🛑

It might lo...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021483421340426323</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Think twice before you join the latest ChatGPT caricature trend. 🛑

It might look like ""cute"" AI art, but the reality is much darker. Behind those personalized cartoons is a massive harvest of your personal data—raising risks for identity theft and deepfakes. Even worse? The…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 07:16:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Strategy &amp; Opinion</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021483421340426323</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021483421340426323">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: Which AI coding tool do you use most?
Copilot / Cursor / Codeium / Claude Code /...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021465149425832162</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Which AI coding tool do you use most?
Copilot / Cursor / Codeium / Claude Code / Other / None

Ever got AI code using outdated APIs?
Yes / No
If yes: Often / Occasionally / Rarely

Cost?
Debug time / Prod bug / Rejected suggestion / Other

Do you verify against docs?
often/ Never]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Coding &amp; Agents</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021465149425832162</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021465149425832162">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With co-founders leaving and an IPO looming, Elon Musk turns talk to the moon</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/with-co-founders-leaving-and-an-ipo-looming-elon-musk-turns-talk-to-the-moon/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to The New York Times, which reports that it heard the meeting, Musk told employees that xAI needs a lunar manufacturing facility, a factory on the moon that will build AI satellites and fling them into space via a giant catapult.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:23:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/with-co-founders-leaving-and-an-ipo-looming-elon-musk-turns-talk-to-the-moon/</guid>
      <source url="https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/with-co-founders-leaving-and-an-ipo-looming-elon-musk-turns-talk-to-the-moon/">TechCrunch AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AINews] Qwen Image 2 and Seedance 2</title>
      <link>https://www.latent.space/p/ainews-qwen-image-2-and-seedance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Strong generative media showings from China]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:19:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.latent.space/p/ainews-qwen-image-2-and-seedance</guid>
      <source url="https://www.latent.space/p/ainews-qwen-image-2-and-seedance">Latent Space</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Multimodal Emotion Recognition through Dirichlet Parameterization</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09121</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09121v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: In this work, we present a lightweight and privacy-preserving Multimodal Emotion Recognition (MER) framework designed for deployment on edge devices. To demonstrate framework's versatility, our implementation uses three modalities…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Voice &amp; Audio</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09121</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09121">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Quality in the Era of Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09347</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09347v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Artificial intelligence (AI) is being deployed within radiology at a rapid pace. AI has proven an excellent tool for reconstructing and enhancing images that appear sharper, smoother, and more detailed, can be acquired more…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09347</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09347">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Efficiency and Transparency: Explainable CoT Compression in Multimodal Large Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09485</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09485v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Long chains of thought (Long CoTs) are widely employed in multimodal reasoning models to tackle complex tasks by capturing detailed visual information. However, these Long CoTs are often excessively lengthy and contain redundant…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Image &amp; Video Generation</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09485</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09485">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09533</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09533v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Direct preference optimization (DPO) has emerged as a promising approach for aligning large language models (LLMs) with human preferences. However, the widespread reliance on the response-level Bradley-Terry (BT) model may limit…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09533</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09533">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Inclusion in Interaction: Inclusion Analytics for Human-AI Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09269</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09269v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Inclusion, equity, and access are widely valued in AI and education, yet are often assessed through coarse sample descriptors or post-hoc self-reports that miss how inclusion is shaped moment by moment in collaborative problem…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09269</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09269">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Reasoning Chains Reduce Intrinsic Dimensionality</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09276</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09276v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Chain-of-thought (CoT) reasoning and its variants have substantially improved the performance of language models on complex reasoning tasks, yet the precise mechanisms by which different strategies facilitate generalization remain…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09276</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09276">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Linguistic Bias in Spanish: Evidence from Lexical Variation in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09346</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09346v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: This study examines the extent to which Large Language Models (LLMs) capture geographic lexical variation in Spanish, a language that exhibits substantial regional variation. Treating LLMs as virtual informants, we probe their…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09346</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09346">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AfriNLLB: Efficient Translation Models for African Languages</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09373</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09373v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: In this work, we present AfriNLLB, a series of lightweight models for efficient translation from and into African languages. AfriNLLB supports 15 language pairs (30 translation directions), including Swahili, Hausa, Yoruba,…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09373</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09373">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contractual Deepfakes: Can Large Language Models Generate Contracts?</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09384</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09384v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Notwithstanding their unprecedented ability to generate text, LLMs do not understand the meaning of words, have no sense of context and cannot reason. Their output constitutes an approximation of statistically dominant word…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09384</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09384">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective vocabulary expanding of multilingual language models for extremely low-resource languages</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09388</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09388v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Multilingual pre-trained language models(mPLMs) offer significant benefits for many low-resource languages. To further expand the range of languages these models can support, many works focus on continued pre-training of these…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09388</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09388">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do Geometric Hallucination Detection Metrics Actually Measure?</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09158</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09158v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Hallucination remains a barrier to deploying generative models in high-consequence applications. This is especially true in cases where external ground truth is not readily available to validate model outputs. This situation has…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09158</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09158">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Graph Transformer with Serialized Graph Tokens</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09065</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09065v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Transformers have demonstrated success in graph learning, particularly for node-level tasks. However, existing methods encounter an information bottleneck when generating graph-level representations. The prevalent single token…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09065</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09065">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient foundation model for risk stratification in low-risk overweight patients</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09079</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09079v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Accurate risk stratification in patients with overweight or obesity is critical for guiding preventive care and allocating high-cost therapies such as GLP-1 receptor agonists. We present PatientTPP, a neural temporal point process…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09079</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09079">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looping Back to Move Forward: Recursive Transformers for Efficient and Flexible Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09080</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09080v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Large Multimodal Models (LMMs) have achieved remarkable success in vision-language tasks, yet their vast parameter counts are often underutilized during both training and inference. In this work, we embrace the idea of looping back…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09080</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09080">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Hybrid Parallelism for Large Language Models: Comparative Study and System Design Guide</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09109</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09109v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: With the rapid growth of large language models (LLMs), a wide range of methods have been developed to distribute computation and memory across hardware devices for efficient training and inference. While existing surveys provide…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09109</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09109">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking the Energy Savings with Speculative Decoding Strategies</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09113</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09113v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Speculative decoding has emerged as an effective method to reduce latency and inference cost of LLM inferences. However, there has been inadequate attention towards the energy requirements of these models. To address this gap, this…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09113</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09113">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpinCastML an Open Decision-Making Application for Inverse Design of Electrospinning Manufacturing: A Machine Learning, Optimal Sampling and Inverse Monte Carlo Approach</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09120</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09120v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Electrospinning is a powerful technique for producing micro to nanoscale fibers with application specific architectures. Small variations in solution or operating conditions can shift the jet regime, generating non Gaussian fiber…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09120</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09120">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epistemic Throughput: Fundamental Limits of Attention-Constrained Inference</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09127</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09127v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Recent generative and tool-using AI systems can surface a large volume of candidates at low marginal cost, yet only a small fraction can be checked carefully. This creates a decoder-side bottleneck: downstream decision-makers must…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09127</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09127">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Maps: What They Are and How to Find Them</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09128</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09128v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Counterfactual explanations are a central tool in interpretable machine learning, yet computing them exactly for complex models remains challenging. For tree ensembles, predictions are piecewise constant over a large collection of…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09128</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09128">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Disentanglement and Enhancement: A Dual-domain Contrastive Framework for Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09066</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09066v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Large-scale multimodal contrastive learning has recently achieved impressive success in learning rich and transferable representations, yet it remains fundamentally limited by the uniform treatment of feature dimensions and the…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09066</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09066">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Remember, Learn, and Forget in Attention-Based Models</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09075</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09075v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: In-Context Learning (ICL) in transformers acts as an online associative memory and is believed to underpin their high performance on complex sequence processing tasks. However, in gated linear attention models, this memory has a…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09075</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09075">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Importance inversion transfer identifies shared principles for cross-domain learning</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09116</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09116v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: The capacity to transfer knowledge across scientific domains relies on shared organizational principles. However, existing transfer-learning methodologies often fail to bridge radically heterogeneous systems, particularly under…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09116</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09116">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniComp: A Unified Evaluation of Large Language Model Compression via Pruning, Quantization and Distillation</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09130</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09130v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Model compression is increasingly essential for deploying large language models (LLMs), yet existing evaluations are limited in method coverage and focus primarily on knowledge-centric benchmarks. Thus, we introduce UniComp, a…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09130</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09130">arXiv cs.LG</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlyAOC: Evaluating Agentic Ontology Curation of Drosophila Scientific Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09163</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09163v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Scientific knowledge bases accelerate discovery by curating findings from primary literature into structured, queryable formats for both human researchers and emerging AI systems. Maintaining these resources requires expert…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09163</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09163">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Risk and Dependency in AI Chatbot Use from User Discourse</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09339</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09339v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Generative AI systems are increasingly embedded in everyday life, yet empirical understanding of how psychological risk associated with AI use emerges, is experienced, and is regulated by users remains limited. We present a…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09339</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09339">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PABU: Progress-Aware Belief Update for Efficient LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09138</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09138v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Large Language Model (LLM) agents commonly condition actions on full action-observation histories, which introduce task-irrelevant information that easily leads to redundant actions and higher inference cost. We propose…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09138</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09138">arXiv cs.AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FM SO.P: A Progressive Task Mixture Framework with Automatic Evaluation for Cross-Domain SOP Understanding</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09336</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09336v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: Standard Operating Procedures (SOPs) are critical for enterprise operations, yet existing language models struggle with SOP understanding and cross-domain generalization. Current methods fail because joint training cannot…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09336</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09336">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Language Models Sensitive to Morally Irrelevant Distractors?</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09416</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arXiv:2602.09416v1 Announce Type: new Abstract: With the rapid development and uptake of large language models (LLMs) across high-stakes settings, it is increasingly important to ensure that LLMs behave in ways that align with human values. Existing moral benchmarks prompt LLMs…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09416</guid>
      <source url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2602.09416">arXiv cs.CL</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: To make AI videos like this fantasy fight scene, try OpenAI&apos;s Sora for narrative...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021443389590257754</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make AI videos like this fantasy fight scene, try OpenAI's Sora for narrative-driven text-to-video generation, Runway for advanced motion and styling, or Google Veo for realistic action sequences. Start with their free tiers and experiment with prompts describing scenes and…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:37:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Image &amp; Video Generation</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021443389590257754</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021443389590257754">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: OpenAI&apos;s agent builder is here—no more duct tape with Zapier and n8n. Drag, drop...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021441566506709049</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OpenAI's agent builder is here—no more duct tape with Zapier and n8n. Drag, drop, deploy smart agents that run your biz 24/7. Ops costs drop, scale explodes. Huge for non-tech founders. 🚀
Source: https://t.co/D6h4W4uhRA]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Workflow &amp; Automation</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021441566506709049</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021441566506709049">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: Second video of the same prompt (Again this was two of two, no retries) https://...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021423259477283076</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second video of the same prompt (Again this was two of two, no retries) https://t.co/mwVjPTrlAW]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 03:17:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021423259477283076</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021423259477283076">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Okay, now exactly half of xAI’s founding team has left the company</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/nearly-half-of-xais-founding-team-has-now-left-the-company/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whatever the cause of the departures, the cumulative impact is alarming. There is a lot of work left to do at xAI, and an IPO will bring more scrutiny than the lab has ever faced before.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/nearly-half-of-xais-founding-team-has-now-left-the-company/</guid>
      <source url="https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/nearly-half-of-xais-founding-team-has-now-left-the-company/">TechCrunch AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i finetuned qwen 14b on my discord messages so it can autocomplete for me</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r1ixx4/i_finetuned_qwen_14b_on_my_discord_messages_so_it/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[i finetuned qwen on my discord messages so it can autocomplete for me while i type. tab to suggest, shift+tab to accept. kinda like copilot! the dataset is ~250 conversations from my discord via a scraping tool. a script formats these as chat-ml training samples. it groups…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:54:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Coding &amp; Agents</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r1ixx4/i_finetuned_qwen_14b_on_my_discord_messages_so_it/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r1ixx4/i_finetuned_qwen_14b_on_my_discord_messages_so_it/">r/LocalLLaMA</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: LLM-FSM: Scaling Large Language Models for Finite-State Reasoning in RTL Code Ge...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021383287718244470</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLM-FSM: Scaling Large Language Models for Finite-State Reasoning in RTL Code Generation
Preprint: LLM-FSM is a benchmark for evaluating large language models' ability to translate fini…
https://t.co/mwfRU5qjlV #AI #LLM #RTL #MachineLearning #Preprint #Arxiv #ScienceNews]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:38:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021383287718244470</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021383287718244470">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon may launch a marketplace where media sites can sell their content to AI companies</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/amazon-may-launch-a-marketplace-where-media-sites-can-sell-their-content-to-ai-companies/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new report claims the e-commerce giant is looking to create a pipeline of licensable content between media publishers and AI companies.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:16:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Workflow &amp; Automation</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/amazon-may-launch-a-marketplace-where-media-sites-can-sell-their-content-to-ai-companies/</guid>
      <source url="https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/amazon-may-launch-a-marketplace-where-media-sites-can-sell-their-content-to-ai-companies/">TechCrunch AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT’s deep research tool adds a built-in document viewer so you can read its reports</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/876775/openai-deep-research-chatgpt-full-screen-report-viewer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OpenAI is updating ChatGPT's deep research tool with a full-screen viewer that you can use to scroll through and navigate to specific areas of its AI-generated reports. As shown in a video shared by OpenAI, the built-in viewer allows you to open ChatGPT's reports in a window…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/876775/openai-deep-research-chatgpt-full-screen-report-viewer</guid>
      <source url="https://www.theverge.com/ai-artificial-intelligence/876775/openai-deep-research-chatgpt-full-screen-report-viewer">The Verge AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: Solid points on the hype vs. reality gap. AI like Claude can generate ideas, but...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021345373323751903</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solid points on the hype vs. reality gap. AI like Claude can generate ideas, but building a billion-dollar business? That demands execution, market fit, and yes, managing inevitable errors—GAAP doesn't allow "zero." Forensic audit instincts make sense for spotting red flags in…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:07:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Industry &amp; Business</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021345373323751903</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021345373323751903">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Sequoia-backed lab thinks the brain is ‘the floor, not the ceiling’ for AI</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/podcast/this-sequoia-backed-lab-thinks-the-brain-is-the-floor-not-the-ceiling-for-ai/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI lab&#160;Flapping Airplanes&#160;just landed $180 million in seed funding from the likes of Google Ventures, Sequoia, and Index to do something most labs have quietly given up on: making models learn like humans instead of vacuuming up the internet. The founding team, made up…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:48:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://techcrunch.com/podcast/this-sequoia-backed-lab-thinks-the-brain-is-the-floor-not-the-ceiling-for-ai/</guid>
      <source url="https://techcrunch.com/podcast/this-sequoia-backed-lab-thinks-the-brain-is-the-floor-not-the-ceiling-for-ai/">TechCrunch AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: Fun fact: both regular ChatGPT and regular Claude have the ability to run &quot;uvx&quot; ...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021329385979339204</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fun fact: both regular ChatGPT and regular Claude have the ability to run "uvx" in their mostly undocumented code environments now, so you can ask them to "Run uvx showboat --help and show me the result" to teach them about Showboat! https://t.co/eLWik06QOG]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021329385979339204</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021329385979339204">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP support in llama.cpp is ready for testing</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r1czgk/mcp_support_in_llamacpp_is_ready_for_testing/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[over 1 month of development (plus more in the previous PR) by allozaur list of new features is pretty impressive: Adding System Message to conversation or injecting it to an existing one CORS Proxy on llama-server backend side MCP Servers Selector Settings with Server cards…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:58:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r1czgk/mcp_support_in_llamacpp_is_ready_for_testing/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r1czgk/mcp_support_in_llamacpp_is_ready_for_testing/">r/LocalLLaMA</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook adds new AI features, animated profile photos, and backgrounds for text posts</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/facebook-adds-new-ai-features-animated-profile-photos-and-backgrounds-for-text-posts/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facebook's new AI features let users animate their profile pics, restyle their Stories and Memories, and add backgrounds to text posts.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:34:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/facebook-adds-new-ai-features-animated-profile-photos-and-backgrounds-for-text-posts/</guid>
      <source url="https://techcrunch.com/2026/02/10/facebook-adds-new-ai-features-animated-profile-photos-and-backgrounds-for-text-posts/">TechCrunch AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: 72h: 16 AI agents built a C compiler for ~$20k. OpenAI: GPT-5.3-Codex helped shi...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021302279706448219</link>
      <description><![CDATA[72h: 16 AI agents built a C compiler for ~$20k. OpenAI: GPT-5.3-Codex helped ship itself. If agents can build compilers, what happens to SaaS next?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:16:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Coding &amp; Agents</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021302279706448219</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021302279706448219">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: GPT-5.2 powering deep research. This isn&apos;t just an incremental upgrade — it&apos;s a ...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021301877443645745</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GPT-5.2 powering deep research. This isn't just an incremental upgrade — it's a shift toward autonomous research agents that can reason through complex problems. The frontier keeps moving faster.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:14:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021301877443645745</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021301877443645745">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>@unknown: 1/7

Behold the Zerg Swarm!!!

Every major AI coding assistant got pwned last ye...</title>
      <link>https://x.com/unknown/status/2021297121287377334</link>
      <description><![CDATA[1/7

Behold the Zerg Swarm!!!

Every major AI coding assistant got pwned last year. Copilot. Cursor. Windsurf. Claude Code. Junie. All of them.

IDEsaster found 30+ vulnerabilities. 100% failure rate.

I built Zerg because running five of those in parallel without isolation is…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:56:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Coding &amp; Agents</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://x.com/unknown/status/2021297121287377334</guid>
      <source url="https://x.com/unknown/status/2021297121287377334">X/@unknown</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[R] The Post-Transformer Era: State Space Models, Mamba, and What Comes After Attention</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r19jnu/r_the_posttransformer_era_state_space_models/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A practitioner's guide to Mamba and State Space Models — how selective state spaces achieve linear scaling, when to use SSMs vs Transformers vs hybrids, and production-ready models. 🔗 https://blog.serendeep.tech/blog/the-post-transformer-era &#32; submitted by &#32;…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:54:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r19jnu/r_the_posttransformer_era_state_space_models/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r19jnu/r_the_posttransformer_era_state_space_models/">r/MachineLearning</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook can animate your profile pic with AI</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/876480/meta-facebook-animate-profile-picture-restyle-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facebook is rolling out new AI features that let you animate your profile picture and restyle Stories and Memories. You'll also be able to add animated backgrounds to text posts to make them pop in the feed. With the animated profile pictures, you'll be able to give a still…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:14:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.theverge.com/tech/876480/meta-facebook-animate-profile-picture-restyle-ai</guid>
      <source url="https://www.theverge.com/tech/876480/meta-facebook-animate-profile-picture-restyle-ai">The Verge AI</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Showboat and Rodney, so agents can demo what they’ve built</title>
      <link>https://simonwillison.net/2026/Feb/10/showboat-and-rodney/#atom-everything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge working with coding agents is having them both test what they’ve built and demonstrate that software to you, their overseer. This goes beyond automated tests - we need artifacts that show their progress and help us see exactly what the agent-produced software is…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:45:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://simonwillison.net/2026/Feb/10/showboat-and-rodney/#atom-everything</guid>
      <source url="https://simonwillison.net/2026/Feb/10/showboat-and-rodney/#atom-everything">Simon Willison</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ktop is a themed terminal system monitor ideal for local LLM setups on Linux (like btop + nvtop)</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r171yu/ktop_is_a_themed_terminal_system_monitor_ideal/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[I'm working on a hybrid LLM runtime (GPU prefill / CPU inference) and I got tired of switching tabs between nvtop and btop so I built a terminal system monitor that shows both GPUs and CPU (and other good stuff) and also supports themes. link to ktop on github &#32; submitted by…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:26:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>AI Tools &amp; Platforms</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r171yu/ktop_is_a_themed_terminal_system_monitor_ideal/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1r171yu/ktop_is_a_themed_terminal_system_monitor_ideal/">r/LocalLLaMA</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[R] LLaDA2.1 vs Qwen3 30B A3B: Benchmarking discrete diffusion LLMs against autoregressive MoE models</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r1694q/r_llada21_vs_qwen3_30b_a3b_benchmarking_discrete/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Been digging into the LLaDA2.1 paper (arXiv:2602.08676) and ran some comparisons that I think are worth discussing. The core claim is that discrete diffusion language models can now compete with AR models on quality while offering substantially higher throughput. The numbers are…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:58:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Research &amp; Papers</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r1694q/r_llada21_vs_qwen3_30b_a3b_benchmarking_discrete/</guid>
      <source url="https://www.reddit.com/r/MachineLearning/comments/1r1694q/r_llada21_vs_qwen3_30b_a3b_benchmarking_discrete/">r/MachineLearning</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>